[Sarutobi Ayame, a.k.a. Sachan, a former elite Oniwabanshu ninja.]
[The target to terminate this time is the unscrupulous loan shark, Nezumiya.]
♪♪～
(根津三屋)ﾍｯﾍｯﾍ…｡
越後屋 おぬしもﾜﾙよのぅ｡
Echigoya, you're quite an evil rascal! Omiya must be cursing you from the afterworld.
近江屋も あの世で
おぬしを恨んでいよう｡
(越後屋)お戯れを…｡
ｱﾔﾂめを殺す算段を整えたのは➡
Surely you jest...
You were the one who set up his murder, Nezumiya-sama.
根津三屋様…
あなた様のほうではありませぬか｡
That was you.
あれ？ そうだったっけ？
Oh? Is that so?
また これ とぼけちゃって！
There you go joking again!
(根津三屋と越後屋の笑い声)
♪♪～
I hope we can continue to do business together.
(越後屋)これからも よきに｡
(物音)
(越後屋)なんだ？ 誰かいるのか？
What is it? Is someone there?
…うわぁっ！
(根津三屋)な… 何奴だ!?
Wh-Who are you?!
(越後屋)ぐはぁっ！
(さっちゃん)祇園精舎の鐘の声
諸行無常の響きあり｡
Like the sound of the bell at Gion Temple, nothing is permanent...
(さっちゃん)沙羅双樹の花の色｡
The color of the blossoms on the twin sandalwood trees...
鬼畜外道 必殺の理をあらわす｡
gives us cause to bring death to fiends and villains.
こんばんは
始末屋さっちゃん 見参｡
Good evening. Sachan, the assassin, has come.
(さっちゃん)闇商人 根津三屋…
か弱き民衆を くいものにし➡
Black market merchant Nezumiya.
You preyed on the weak common folk...
己の私腹を肥やすこと
万死に値する｡
to fill your own pockets. An act deserving of ten thousand deaths.
この 始末屋さっちゃんが
成敗してくれよう！
I, assassin Sachan, shall punish you.
(根津三屋)おい… こっちだぞ｡
Hey, hey, I'm over here!
さぁ 覚悟しなさい 根津三屋！
Prepare to die, Nezumiya!
What did you come here for?!
(根津三屋)何しにきたの お前！
(さっちゃん)あの すみません…｡
Oh, I'm sorry...
さっきのあれで
ﾒｶﾞﾈ 落としちゃって…｡
I dropped my glasses earlier.
ちょっと 一緒に
探してくれませんか？
Would you help me find them?
(配下)ほら｡
あ すみません｡
Here.
Oh, thank you.
Ah, now I can see what I'm...
あぁ 見えてきた 見えてきた｡
…見えなきゃよかった｡
I wish I couldn't see now...
(配下)曲者！
ふっ！
Intruder!
My plan has failed! Retreat!
作戦失敗！ 退却よ！
(政/勇二)えぇ～っ!?
What?!
(配下)逃げたぞ～！
(配下)追え！ 逃がすな!!
She's getting away!
After her!
♪♪～
I messed up...
しくじったか…
しかたないわ 出直そう｡
I have no choice. I'll return later.
♪♪～
(さっちゃん)うわっ!!
["Marriage Is Prolonging an Illusion for Your Whole Life"]
(新八)おはようございま～す！
Good morning!
(お登勢)あら 新八かい おはよう｡
Oh, Shinpachi? Morning.
お登勢さん 今日は早いですね｡
You're early today, Otose-san.
ｱﾝﾀんとこの連中が ｸﾞｰﾀﾗなだけさ｡
It's because all you guys are such goof-offs.
そりゃそうと 先月の家賃
今日までに払ってもらう約束だよ｡
By the way, you promised to pay last month's rent by today.
ろくでなしの主人に
伝えておいておくれ｡
Give that message to my good-for-nothing tenant.
あ… はい｡ すみません｡
Uh...right. I'm sorry.
はぁ… ｱｲﾂも いいかげん
結婚でもして➡
It's about time he got married and learned a little responsibility.
責任感っつうものを ちょっとは
覚えてもらいたいもんだねぇ｡
ｱﾊﾊ… そうですね｡
Yes, you're right...
《銀さんが 結婚か…
絶対 ありえないな》
Gin-san married...?
It could never happen...
おはようございま～す｡ あれ？
Good morning.
Huh? Where is everyone, Sadaharu?
定春 みんなは？
(定春)ｱｳ？
はぁ… ﾎﾝﾄに ｸﾞｰﾀﾗな連中だなぁ｡
They really are goof-offs.
は～い 起きて 朝だよ｡
Okay, get up. It's morning.
銀さ～ん 結野ｱﾅの お天気注意報
始まっちゃいま… いっ!?
Gin-san! Ms. Ketsuno Ana's morning Weather Alert is about to...
Huh? What're you doing, Shinpachi?
(神楽)何やってるか？ 新八｡
来るな…！
Don't come any closer!
銀ちゃんに 何かあったｱﾙか？
Did something happen to Gin-chan?
ｽﾄﾊﾟｰか!? ｽﾄﾊﾟｰになってたｱﾙか!?
Why are you trying to stop me?!
Have you become his stopper?!
やめろ！ あっちには➡
Stop! There's nothing but a filthy world in there!
薄汚れた世界しか
広がってねえぞ!!
Unh... What is it...? You're making too much noise...
(銀時)
なんだよ… やかましいなぁ｡
あ？
んん!?
So, who is this person?
で… この人 誰？
ｱﾝﾀが連れ込んだんでしょうが｡
You're the one who brought her here!
昨日は… あぁ ﾀﾞﾒだ➡
Yesterday...
It's no use. All I remember is up until I went drinking.
飲みにいったとこまでしか
思い出せねえや｡
You're going to play dumb after engaging in ninja cosplay?
忍者のｺｽﾌﾟﾚまでして
とぼけないでくださいよ｡
Is she a kunoichi? Did you do kunoichi role-playing?
[Kunoichi is a term for a female ninja, often highly sexualized.]
くの一か？ くの一ﾌﾟﾚｰか？
いいかげんにしろよ！
んなことするわけねえだろ！
Cut it out! I wouldn't do a thing like that!
どっちかっていうと
ﾅｰｽのほうがいい｡
You know I'm into nurse costumes.
Are you telling the truth?
ﾎﾝﾄかなぁ？
(神楽)新八～｡
Shinpachi.
男は 若いうちに
遊んでたほうがいいｱﾙよ｡
Men should play around while they're young.
じゃないと いい歳こいてから
若い女に騙されたり➡
If they don't, when they're older, they'll be tricked by young women,
変な遊びにﾊﾏったりするって
ﾏﾐｰが言ってたよ｡
or become obsessed with weird fetishes.
That's what Mommy told me.
お前のﾏﾐｰも 苦労したんだな｡
Your mommy went through a lot, didn't she?
あの～ ｵﾚ
何も覚えてないんすけど➡
Uh, I...don't remember anything. Did I do anything strange?
何か変なことしましたか？
いいえ 何も｡
No, nothing.
そうかそうか よかった｡
I see, I see. That's great.
I thought maybe for sure I did something wrong while I was drunk.
ｵﾚは てっきり 酒の勢いで
何か間違いを起こしたのかと…｡
There are no "mistakes" between husband and wife.
夫婦の間に 間違いなんてないわ｡
I'll go along with any of your crazy desires.
どんなﾏﾆｱｯｸな要望にも
私は応えるわ｡
I beg your pardon?
はい？
さぁ あなた➡
Now, Dear...
納豆が
こんなにﾈﾊﾞﾈﾊﾞに練れましたよ｡
Look how sticky the natto has become.
Say "aah."
はい あ～ん｡
ｱﾀﾀﾀﾀ…｡
Ow-ow-ow.
そこ 口じゃないから｡
目は 口ほどにものを言う って➡
That's not my mouth.
They say the eyes are as expressive as the mouth, but that's not my mouth.
いうけど 口じゃないから｡
ってか なに？ 夫婦って！
What do you mean, "husband and wife"?
You will take responsibility, won't you? After doing what you did.
責任とってくれるんでしょ？
あんなことしたんだから｡
あんなことって なんだよ！
何もしてねえよ ｵﾚは！
What do you mean "what I did"? I didn't do anything!
What're you talking about?
(さっちゃん)なに言ってるの｡
この納豆のように➡
We were entwined with each other like this natto.
絡み合った仲じゃない｡
…ｱｲﾀｯ 痛い｡
Ow-ow-ow.
I told you, that's not your mouth!
だから そこ 口じゃねえって
言ってんだろ！
銀さん やっちゃったもんは
しかたないよ｡ 認知しよう｡
Gin-san, you can't change what you did. Accept it.
結婚は 惚れるより慣れｱﾙよ｡
They say marriage is more about becoming familiar with one another than love.
ｵﾒｴらまで なに言ってんの｡
What're you guys talking about?!
Your beloved Gin-san's about to be taken away by crazy natto girl!
みんなの銀さんが
納豆女に取られちゃうよ!?
冗談じゃねえよ｡ ｵﾚが
何も覚えてねえのをいいことに➡
This is ridiculous!
You're trying to trick me by using the fact that I don't remember anything!
騙そうとしてんだろ｡
な？ だいたい ﾎﾞｸら➡
In the first place, we don't even know each other's names, so how can we talk about marriage?
お互いの名前も知らないのにさぁ
結婚だなんて…｡
とぼけた顔して…｡
体は知ってるくせにさぁ｡
You act as if you don't know.
But our bodies know.
Stop talking like that!
And that's not me!
ｲﾔなこと言うんじゃねえよ！
それから それ銀さんじゃねえぞ!!
If your eyes are that bad,
put on your glasses!
つか 目 悪いなら ﾒｶﾞﾈかけなよ！
落ちてましたよ これ！
They fell off. Here!
(さっちゃん)というわけで…
さっちゃんと申します｡
So, that's what happened.
My name is Sachan.
Please make me happy for life, my husband.
どうぞ 末永く
幸せにしてくださいね 旦那様｡
Uh...likewise. Please be good to us, too.
あぁ どうも｡
こちらこそ よろしく｡
I prefer fish to meat for dinner, okay.
夕飯は 肉より魚で お願いね｡
わぁ 受け入れるの はやっ！
つうか 銀さん こっちだってば！
You're too quick to accept her!
Gin-san is over here!
《ﾌｯ… 追っ手をかわすため➡
I'll lay low here for a while to throw off my pursuers.
しばらく ここに
身を潜めさせてもらうわ》
(さっちゃんの鼻歌)
ﾎﾝﾄに ここに
居座る気みたいですね｡
Looks like she's serious about staying here.
どうするんすか？ 銀さん｡
What are you going to do, Gin-san?
A woman who's serious is harder to get rid of than the fat in pork broth ramen.
本気になった女は
こってり背脂ﾄﾝｺﾂﾗｰﾒﾝより➡
しつこいｱﾙ｡
まいったなぁ｡
Good grief.
こういうときは 糖分で
気を落ち着かせるしかねえな｡
Times like this, all I can do is calm myself down with something sweet.
《ﾌｯ 簡単に
言うこと聞いちゃうんだから…｡
He listens to what I say with no problem.
男って ﾊﾞｶな生き物ね｡
Men are such stupid creatures.
All I have to do now is play the cute, obedient, young wife.
あとは かわいくて従順な
若妻さえ 演じれば…》
あぁ～っ！
Hey, anyone seen the pudding that I put in the fridge?
おい！ 冷蔵庫に入れてあった
ｵﾚのﾌﾟﾘﾝ 知らねえか？
(新八/神楽)ううん｡
あの～ 冷蔵庫にあったﾌﾟﾘ…｡
You know, the pudding I had in the fridge.
あぁん もう～
せっかく隠してたのに～｡
Oh come on! And I tried to hide it, too!
しようがないな～
この 食いしん坊さん｡
I guess I have no choice, you piggy you!
は？
今日は 何の日でしょう？
Huh?
What day is it today?
何ですか？ 生ｺﾞﾐの日？
賞味期限 きれてたっけ？
What is it? Garbage day? The expiration date on a food package?
もう～ 忘れたの？
Oh come on! You've already forgotten?
It's the anniversary of the day we spent together!
さっちゃんたちが
つきあった記念日だよ｡
We just met a while ago.
さっき
会ったばっかなんですけど…｡
Hasn't your personality changed?
っていうか 最初と
ｷｬﾗ変わってません？
Ta-da!
ｼﾞｬ～ﾝ！ 記念の 納豆ﾌﾟﾘﾝで～す！
Natto pudding for our anniversary!
Am I being punished for something?
なんの罰ｹﾞｰﾑですか？ これは｡
今日は特別に ２人の好きなものを
一緒にしてみました｡
Today, I've made a special combination of our two favorite things!
はい あ～んして｡
Now, open wide...
ふざけんな!!
ｷｬｰｰｯ!!
Enough of this!
おい 押しかけ女房のあとは➡
Hey, after pushing yourself on me as my wife, you're going to sully my pudding?!
さっそく ｵﾚのかわいいﾌﾟﾘﾝに
嫌がらせか？ ﾃﾒｴ｡
The hierarchy in this household starts with me.
この家のﾊﾟﾜｰﾊﾞﾗﾝｽは まずｵﾚ！
次に 甘味だ｡ 覚えとけ！
After that, it's sweets. Remember that!
おい！ 甘味が ﾅﾝﾊﾞｰ２かよ!?
Hey! Sweets are number two?!
《こっちが
下手に出てるからって…｡
I didn't play this right...
Bear it. Bear it, Sachan.
耐えるのよ…
耐えるのよ さっちゃん》
そんなに照れないでいいのよ｡
はい お食べ｡
You don't have to be shy about it. Now have some.
I'm not going to eat this!
こんなもん 食えるかぁ～!!
It's okay. This is actually pretty good.
大丈夫よ これ｡ 案外 ｲｹるｱﾙ｡
お前が食うな！
Don't eat it!
ﾃﾒｴで食わねえのに 勝手に ﾌﾟﾘﾝに
納豆 ｺﾗﾎﾞﾚｰｼｮﾝさせんな ﾊﾞｶ野郎｡
You're not going to eat it,
so don't go trying to create a collaboration between the pudding and natto, fool!
Are you trying to be a producer?!
ﾌﾟﾛﾃﾞｭｰｻｰ気取りかよ｡
ｶｰﾃﾞｨｶﾞﾝ 肩から かけんぞ！
I'll hang a cardigan over your shoulders.
《く… 屈辱だわ｡
かつては 幕府のお庭番…➡
This is humiliating.
I was once one of the elite Oniwabanshu-why should I be subjected to this verbal abuse.
ｴﾘｰﾄの この私が
なんで こんな蔑みの言葉を…》
ここの掟が守れねえなら
出ていけ｡ この ｸｽﾞ女！
If you can't abide by these rules, then get out, you worthless woman!
《でも なに？ この感覚…》
But what is this? This feeling...
ﾌﾝ！ 何か甘いもん買ってくらぁ｡
I'm going out to buy something sweet.
あっ 待って！
Wait!
っていうか…
どうしたら そうなんの!?
How'd you end up like that?
納豆が… 納豆が～！
The natto...it's sucking me in.
Why're you following me?
And what's with that outfit?
なに ついてきてんだよ｡
ていうか なに？ その格好｡
Men like young wives, right?
男の人は 若妻が好きでしょ？
That's certainly a young wife's look,
たしかに それも若妻だけど
そんな若妻 好きなの➡
but only Masuo-kun would like a young wife who looks like that.
ﾏｽｵ君くらいだぞ｡
それ 違う人よ｡
That's someone else.
《この変装なら
追っ手も 気づかないわね｡
My pursuers won't recognize me in this costume.
あとは かわいくて従順な
若妻さえ 演じれば…》
Now all I have to do is play the cute, obedient, young wife.
あ…｡
どうしたの？
What's the matter?
なんでもねえよ｡
Nothing.
(さっちゃん)あっ！
You just looked at that woman, didn't you?
ねぇ 今 あの女の人
見てたでしょ？
ふ～ん ああいう人が好きなんだ｡
Hmph. Is she your type?
んなわけねえだろ｡
ﾃﾒｴ ｵﾚを ﾏﾆｱに仕立てる魂胆か？
No way! Are you trying to make me out to be a weirdo?!
何やってんだい？
こんなところで｡
What're you doing out here?
どちら様ですか？
Who might you be?
Who am I? Who are you?
どちら様って…
ｱﾝﾀが 何者だい？ 銀時～｡
Gintoki?
銀時… って 呼び捨てに！
別に なんでもねえよ｡
You showed him no respect.
It's no big thing.
By the way, Gintoki, you said that by today, you'd pay last month's...
そういえば 銀時 今日までに
先月分 払うっていう…｡
ちょっと！ 銀時 銀時って
気安く話しかけないでよ｡
Just a minute. Don't talk to him so affectionately.
悪いけど 銀さんは
もう 私のものなのよ！
I'm sorry, but Gin-san is already...
mine!
What's with that woman? All I did was ask you to pay me!
(お登勢)なんなんだい あの女は｡
ｱﾀｼは お前に 金 払えって
話してるだけだよ｡
慰謝料ね？
あなただって楽しんだんでしょ？
So it's alimony you want, is it?
You had your fun, too! You don't deserve any money!
そんなの必要ないわ～！
What's that girl talking about?
なに言ってんだい？ あの子は｡
You're nothing but a woman from his past.
Immerse yourself in your old memories.
どうせ あなたは 過去の女｡
昔の思い出に浸ってなさい｡
Hey! You think this is my former girlfriend?!
おい！ これが ｵﾚの元ｶﾉか？
You really must think I'm a weirdo among weirdos!
ｵﾚは ﾏﾆｱの中でも
選ばれしﾏﾆｱか！
I'm going to beat the both of you!
ｵﾒｴら ２人とも ぶん殴るよ！
あっ！ もしかして お義母様？
お義母様ですか!?
Could she be your mother? Is she your mother?!
おい～！ 母ちゃん
こんなんだったら➡
Hey, if my mother were like this, I'd have become a delinquent in middle school!
中学んとき ぜってえｸﾞﾚるぞ！
頭 ﾊﾟﾝﾁにすんぞ!!
I'd have had a punch perm!
今 ｵﾒｴに ﾊﾟﾝﾁくれてやろうか！
Shall I give you a punch right now?!
どうか ご無礼をお許しください
お義母様｡
Please forgive my rudeness, Mother.
なんなんだい？ この女｡
あ～ あれだ｡
What's with this girl?
She, you know, hit her head when she tripped and fell after chasing a stray cat that ran off with a fish.
お魚くわえた ﾄﾞﾗ猫
追っかけてる拍子に 転んで➡
She's a little light in the head and enjoys cosplay.
頭 打って 陽気になっちゃった
ｺｽﾌﾟﾚ女だ｡
《公衆の面前で
こんな ぞんざいな扱いされて…｡
To be treated this rudely in public...
Yet why, again, do I feel...
それなのに なんで…？
また この 心のざわめき…｡
This stirring in my heart...
もっと…
もっと いじめてほしい！》
More... I want him to torment me more...
(お登勢)どうしちゃったんだい？
この女は｡
What's wrong with this girl?
(ｶﾗｽの鳴き声)
もう～ 銀さんが
しっかりしないから➡
Man!
Gin-san wasn't firm with her, so now she really does plan on staying here!
ﾎﾝﾄに あの人
ここに居座る気ですよ｡
いいかげん ﾋﾞｼｯと 男らしいとこ➡
Isn't it about time you showed her you're a man?
見せたほうが
いいんじゃないですか？
But I really did try.
いやぁ… ｵﾚも
がんばってんだけどよ～｡
《ﾌｯ あの男は もう 私の虜｡
That man is smitten with me.
男って ﾊﾞｶな生き物ね｡
Men are foolish creatures.
…でも 時々 訪れる
この 胸の高鳴りは なに？》
But what is this occasional throbbing in my heart?
[TEL]
…ぶっ！
(神楽)ただいまよ～｡
I'm back.
銀ちゃん まさか！
Gin-chan, you don't think she's...?!
You mean?!
まさか～！
え… ｵﾚ？
What? Me?
そんな… まさか…｡
That couldn't be...
[TEL]
もしもし？ さっちゃんですけど｡
Hello? Sachan speaking.
[TEL](根津三屋)やぁ 始末屋さん｡
あなたは！
Hello there, Miss Assassin.
You're...!
Nice to meet you last night. I'm glad to hear your voice again.
[TEL]ゆうべは どうも｡
声が聞けて 嬉しいよ｡
美しい始末屋さんに➡
I think I've fallen in love with the beautiful assassin.
どうやら 私は
恋をしてしまったようでねぇ｡
Nezumiya?!
根津三屋！
I got your cellular number from...
屋敷に忍び込んでた ｷﾐの友人から
ｹｰﾀｲ番号 ｹﾞｯﾂしちゃったよ｡
your friends who snuck into my home.
[TEL](根津三屋)ぜひ また
会いたいんだが 来てくれるよね？
I'd really like to meet you again.
You will come, won't you?
The stars may change, but the importance of one's friends...
[TEL]星は変わっても 友人の大切さに
変わりはないからね｡
never changes, you know.
Well, I'll be waiting.
[TEL]それでは… 待ってるよ｡
(電話が切れる音)
おい｡
Hey.
I've decided to deal with this. I'm an honorable man.
腹くくったよ｡
ｵﾚも男だ… 記憶にねえとはいえ➡
Even though I can't remember any of it,
あんなことしといて
知らんぷりもできねえ｡
I can't ignore you after what I did to you.
こんなｵﾚでよかったら
もらってください！
If you'll settle for a guy like me, then, please marry me.
♪♪～
Are...you serious, Gin-san?!
ﾏ… ﾏｼﾞっすか 銀さん！
I see. Then come with me.
そう…｡ じゃあ 一緒に来て｡
式場ですか？
ｵﾚ あんまり 金ないんですけど…｡
To the wedding hall?
I don't have too much money.
Ow-ow-ow! Just a minute...
ちょ… ちょっと！
初めてだから 優しくしてね～！
This is my first time, so please be gentle!
I'd better be careful of women, too.
ﾎﾞｸも 女には気をつけよう｡
Shinpachi!
(神楽)新八～｡
どうしたの？
あれ｡
What's the matter?
That.
この穴… いつから開いてたの？
How long has that hole been here?
Sachan might be an angel from the heavens.
(神楽)さっちゃん
空から落ちてきた天女かも｡
まずは お父さんに
会ってもらうから｡
First, you need to meet my father.
An introduction, huh? I've come this far. Might as well keep going.
挨拶か…｡ ま こうなったら
どこへでも行くけどな｡
ただ なんで こんなとこ
通っていかなきゃならねえの？
But why do we have to go this way?
I was raised in a very strict house, so I have a curfew.
(さっちゃん)私 箱入り娘だから
門限 厳しいの｡
いや 確かに 立派な箱だけどよ…｡
Well, you guys sure have a nice, big house.
え なに お義父さん 怖い人なの？
いったい どんな人なの？
What?
Is your father a scary guy?
What kind of person is he?
He's an unscrupulous loan shark with hair all over his body and buckteeth.
体中 毛だらけで 出っ歯の
悪徳高利貸しよ｡
なんだ おい｡
What's with that?
Are you at that age when you don't want to do your panties in the same wash as his?
お父さんとは ﾊﾟﾝﾂも
一緒に洗いたくない年頃か？
Every girl reaches that age eventually.
女の子には そういう時期が
必ず くるんだよ｡
But try to remember-wasn't your father your first love?
でも お前 思い出してみろ
初恋の相手は お父さんだったろ？
新婚生活 始まったら そういうの
全部 注意していくからな ｵﾚは｡
Once we're newlyweds, I'm going to change these bad habits of yours.
関白宣言だから！
(さっちゃん)ｼｯ 静かに｡
I'm declaring my dominance.
Shh... Quiet.
誰だ？ あれ｡
Who's that?
Our manservant, Nakamura-san, the butler.
(さっちゃん)
お手伝いの中村さんよ｡
He's on lookout because I'm coming home late.
私の帰りが遅いから
見回っているんだわ｡
今のうち 言っとくけど
ｵﾚ 束縛するﾀｲﾌﾟだから｡
Let me tell you this now: I'm the type of guy who's pretty restrictive.
結婚したら
奥さんのこと 縛るよ｡
If we get married, I'll bind you to my rules.
Huh? Bind...?
えっ… 縛る？
What is this? Why does the sound of his words cause my chest to tighten so...?
《なに？ この
胸のｷｭﾝとする言葉の響き！
I want to be bound...bind me! Bind me! Tighter!
縛られたい…｡ 縛って！
縛って！ もっと強く～!!》
…あっ｡
Bind...me?
縛るって… 私のことも？
Darn right.
当たりめえだ｡ 女友達の誘い
断れないからって 合ｺﾝ禁止な｡
You won't be able to see your male friends or stay out all night with the girls.
(中村)…ん？
やべっ 中村さん気づいた…➡
Trouble. Nakamura-san saw us.
ぞっ!?
(中村)ぶごぉっ！
(中村)なんだ あれ!?
Wh-What's that?!
(中村)始末屋だ！
始末屋が乗り込んできたぞ!!
It's the assassin! The assassin's back!
中村さ～ん!!
お前 やりすぎだろ！
Nakamura-san!
That's going too far!
Nakamura-san couldn't help it-that's his job!
中村さんだって 仕事で
しかたなく やってんだぞ！
なんか いっぱい来たぞ！
今度は なによ!?
Seems like a lot of them are coming.
Who are they this time?
It's Nakamura B, Nakamura C and Nakamura D.
中村Ｂ 中村Ｃ 中村Ｄよ｡
中村ばっかりじゃねえか！
So...they're all named Nakamura?!
It has begun. Father is testing the groom. Fight hard for me, honey!
始まったわね お父さんの婿試し｡
２人で 共に がんばりましょう｡
え… なに？
Say what?
…あぁっ！
(さっちゃん)いくわよ！
Let's go!
おい！ 旦那を落とすなよ！
Hey! Don't leave your husband!
(配下)申し上げます｡
Allow me to report.
始末屋の女が 見回りの兵を突破し
屋敷内に潜入した模様です｡
The assassin woman has broken through our security and appears to have entered the mansion.
ﾌﾌﾌ…｡
Then set the traps! When you find them, kill them all!
ならば 罠を作動させろ｡
ﾔﾂらを見つけしだい 皆殺しだ！
(配下)はっ｡
Yes, sir!
(根津三屋)飛んで火にいる
夏の虫とは このことだ｡
They're like moths flying into a flame.
ﾊﾊﾊﾊﾊ…｡
(根津三屋)数々の罠を
乗り越えんと➡
They won't reach here unless they get past all the traps.
ここまでは たどりつけん｡
Even if they manage to get here,
万一 たどりつけたとしても
こちらには 人質がいる｡
we have hostages.
必ずや 仕留めてみせるぞ｡
We will finish them off.
Your father must be quite strict.
お義父さん
かなり厳しい人なんだな｡
I'm practically out of work.
Think that's all right?
ｵﾚ ほとんど仕事ないんだけど
大丈夫かな？
It'll be all right. Just as long as he can trust you as a person.
大丈夫よ｡ 人間として
信頼できれば きっと｡
(２人)うわぁ～っ！
Bad! This is really bad! They're here!!
ﾍﾞﾀ～！
ﾍﾞﾀすぎるの きちゃったよ～!!
いったい どうなってんだよ
お前んちは！
What the hell is going on at your house?!
(さっちゃん)婿試しよ｡
道が閉ざされても➡
It's a son-in-law test!
He's trying to see if we can make it together even if the path is closed off.
２人で やっていけるか
見極めているみたい｡
Closed off? It's coming right at us!
閉ざされるっていうか
こっち向かってきてんですけど！
え～っ!?
Hop! Step! Business Jump!
ﾎｯﾌﾟ！ ｽﾃｯﾌﾟ！ ﾋﾞｼﾞﾈｽｼﾞｬ～ﾝﾌﾟ!!
どうやら 私の家を
継ぐという ﾌﾟﾚｯｼｬｰに➡
Seems he is testing whether or not you can withstand the pressure of taking over our House.
耐えられるか 試されたみたい｡
ｵﾚ 逃げっぱなしだったような気が
すんだけど…｡
I think all I was doing was running away.
(早乙女)ﾌｯﾌｯﾌ… 待っていたぞ｡
I've been expecting you.
どちらさん？
元ｶﾚよ｡
Who's this?
My ex-boyfriend. He's working with my father to get in our way.
お父さんと結託して
私たちのｼﾞｬﾏをするつもりだわ｡
今でも 元ｶﾚに会ってるわけ？
You're still seeing your ex-boyfriend?
I seriously can't allow that. I told you I'd bind you to my rules.
ｵﾚ ﾏｼﾞ そういうの許さないよ｡
縛るって言ってんじゃん｡
あの人 ｽﾄｰｶｰ気味なの｡
He's a bit of a stalker.
My foolhardiness gives me license throughout the land!
天下ご免の 向こう見ず～!!
おい 元ｶﾚ｡ 男が あんま
未練ﾀﾗﾀﾗ しつこいってのは…➡
Hey, ex-boyfriend. Men who cling on without letting go...
are boors!
野暮ってもんだろうがぁ～っ!!
ぶは～っ!!
(さっちゃん)先を急ぎましょう｡
はいよ｡
We need to hurry.
Right.
(銀時/さっちゃん)うわぁっ!!
(刺客たち)待て ｺﾗｧ～!!
What's going on here?!
なんなんですか～？
Who are those guys?!
ｱｲﾂら いったい
誰なんだよ 今度は！
Ex-boyfriends.
元ｶﾚよ｡
えっ ｳｿ ﾏｼﾞ？
What? You've got to be kidding! All of them?
全員？ つうか ｵﾚ 何番目だよ！
What number am I?!
困ったわ｡ 早く お父さんに会って
事情を話さなきゃ｡
This isn't good. We have to meet Father quickly and explain the situation.
それじゃ いいから
まず お前が行け｡
All right, then you go on first! I'll come later.
ｵﾚは あとから行くから｡
でも… 銀さんは？
But, what about you, Gin-san?
こんな状況で 女房を
先に行かせねえ夫はいねえよ｡
In a situation like this, no husband would stop his wife from going first.
あ～ 走りづれえ！ こんなんなら
ｽｰﾂにすんだったなぁ まったく！
Gosh, this is hard to run in!
I should've worn a suit!
(さっちゃん)じゃあ 頼んだわね！
I'll be counting on you, then!
Give my regards to Father!
お義父さんに よろしくな～！
ﾍｯ しつけえ野郎どもだ｡
Persistent bastards.
(刺客たち)うぉ～っ！
こっから先は ｵﾚが 一歩も…｡
From here on, I won't allow you to take...
one step...
一歩も…｡
(刺客たち)うおぉ～！
やっぱ ﾑﾘ～!!
On second thought, no way!
(配下)根津三様！
大変です 根津三様！
Nezumi-sama! Trouble! Nezumi-sama!
(配下)始末屋の女が
罠を 次々と破り➡
The assassin woman has bested each of our traps,
こちらに
近づいてきている模様です｡
and she appears to be approaching this way.
Many of the assassins we sent after her have been defeated.
仕向けた刺客たちも
多数やられたとのこと｡
Curses! She doesn't know when to quit!
おのれ 性懲りもなく！
人質が どうなってもいいのか！
Doesn't she care what happens to the hostages?!
こうなったら 総動員だ！
なんとしても ﾔﾂらを始末しろ!!
Since it's come to this, mobilize every last man! Get rid of them at all cost!
(配下たち)はっ！
Yes, sir!
(さっちゃん)根津三様｡
Nezumi-sama.
Their objective is the rescue of the hostages.
(さっちゃん)
ﾔﾂの目的は 人質の救出｡
仲間を はりつけにし➡
I think the best plan would be to bind their friends to posts
and spear them to death in order to stop them from coming.
ﾔﾂの動きを封じるのが 得策かと｡
(根津三屋)うむ｡
Well, then, I...
(さっちゃん)では 私めが…｡
(さっちゃん)あ やばい｡ ﾒｶﾞﾈ ﾒｶﾞﾈ｡
おい｡ どこ行くんだ おい！
Oh no, my glasses. My glasses...
Hey, where are you going?
ｼｰ 静かに｡
私よ 私｡ さっちゃんよ｡
Shh... Be quiet. It's me, Sachan.
今 助けるから
もうちょっと芝居しててよね｡
I'll rescue you now, so play along for a while.
いたぞ 始末屋だ！
There she is! It's the assassin!
(配下)討ち取れ～!!
Kill her!
Sachan! Run!
(勇二/政)さっちゃん 逃げろ！
さっちゃ～ん!!
Sachan!
♪♪～
なっ 何奴じゃ!?
Wh-Who are you?!
♪♪～
必殺始末人 入り婿の銀さん 見参｡
The knockout-blow assassin!
It is I... Gin the groom!
銀さん！
Gin-san!
Father!
お父上～！
Please let me marry...
娘さんを ﾎﾞｸに…➡
your daughter!
くださ～～い!!
♪♪～
(さっちゃん)
銀さん？ ちょっと 銀さん！
Gin-san? Hey, Gin-san!
(さっちゃん)
ごめんなさい 銀さん…｡
Forgive me, Gin-san.
ﾎﾝﾄは 私たち… 何もなかったの｡
The truth is... Nothing happened between us.
なのに…
こんな 利用するようなことを…｡
Yet you... You let me use you like this.
Hey, what're you doing? I'm not hurt there. Did you hear me?
おい なにやってんの？
そんなとこ ｹｶﾞしてねえんだよ｡
おい 聞いてる？
あぁ もういい 触んな｡
なんか 納豆くさい｡
That's enough. Don't touch me. You smell like natto.
こんな 傷の手当ても
できねえんじゃ➡
If you can't even treat wounds like this,
no one will have you as their wife.
嫁のもらい手もねえぞ｡
See you.
じゃあな｡
それからよぉ…➡
Oh, and one more thing...
The next time you want me to help you,
今度 助けてほしいときは➡
don't do all this roundabout stuff and just come to Odd Jobs.
まどろっこしいことしねえで
万事屋に来いや｡
♪♪～
(政)さっちゃん…
ありゃあ 惚れちまったかな｡
Think Sachan's fallen in love?
(勇二)どうだろうねぇ｡
Who knows...
♪♪～
《さっちゃん:ﾌﾌｯ
男って ﾊﾞｶな生き物ね》
Men really are foolish creatures.
おはようございま～す｡
Good morning.
Gin-san! You'll miss Ms. Ketsuno...Ana's morning Weather Alert...
銀さん 結野ｱﾅの お天気注意報
今日も 見逃…｡
Gin-san, bind me tightly...
さぁ 銀さん 私を 強く縛って｡
No, that's not what I meant.
いや そうじゃないから｡
[Preview]
If it isn't Gintoki!
It's me, Tatsuma Sakamoto!
What? A spaceship is about to crash? That's terrible!
The next episode: "When You're in a Fix, Keep on Laughing, Laughing..."
[After winning a drawing for a free trip to space, the Odd Jobs gang sets out.]
[But was the ship space-jacked and in danger of crashing on a planet?!]
♪♪(さっちゃんの歌)
♪♪～